here's a geometric way to compute the
infinite sum of the powers of 1 6 1 6
plus 1 6 squared plus 1 6 cubed and so
on take a circle of Area 1 and draw a
smaller circle inside with Area 1 6.
then the annulus around that Circle can
be divided into five equal pieces all of
size 1 6. we can shade one of them to
represent the Area 1 6. now we can
repeat the process on the inner 1 6
circle taking 1 6 of 1 6 and decomposing
the annular region into five regions of
area 136 or 1 over 6 squared continuing
this process indefinitely produces a
region whose area represents the
infinite sum of the powers of one-sixth
but we also now see that the Shaded area
can be replicated four more times to
fill in this circle therefore the sum of
the powers of 1 6 represents one-fifth
of the full circle